<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment Application</string>
    <string name="heading">Taj</string>
    <string name="content">Jamsetji Nusserwanji Tata, founder of the Tata Group, opened the Taj Mahal Palace, a hotel in Mumbai (formerly called Bombay) overlooking the Arabian Sea, on 16 December 1903. It was the first Taj property and the first Taj hotel. There are several anecdotal stories about why Tata opened the Taj hotel. According to a story, he decided to open the hotel after an incident involving racial discrimination at the Watson\'s Hotel in Mumbai, where he was refused entry as the hotel permitted only Europeans. Hotels that accepted only European guests were very common across British India then. According to another story, he opened the hotel when one of his friends expressed disgust over the hotels that were present in Bombay then. But a more plausible reason was advanced by Lovat Fraser, a close friend of the Tata and one of the early directors of the IHCL group, that the idea had long been in his mind and that he had made a study on the subject. He did not have any desire to own a hotel but he wanted to attract people to India and to improve Bombay. It is said that Jamsetji Tata had travelled to places like London, Paris, Berlin, and Düsseldorf to arrange for materials and pieces of art, furniture and other interior decor for his hotel. The Taj group has since then developed and flourished, under the Tata Group.</string>
    <string name="about">The Taj Mahal Palace opened in Mumbai, then Bombay, in 1903, giving birth to the country’s first harbour landmark. The recently trademarked flagship hotel overlooks the majestic Gateway of India. This legendary 5 star hotel in Mumbai has played host to kings, dignitaries and eminent personalities from across the globe, and is acknowledged as a world leader in hospitality. Each of the rooms 285 rooms and suites are a striking blend of nostalgic elegance, rich history and modern facilities. Strategically located in Mumbai’s prime historical and commercial hub, The Taj Mahal Palace is walking distance from Colaba Causeway, known for its touristy tiny roadside shops. The city’s financial hub, parliament, stadium, offices and shopping districts are all located within close proximity; as is a flourishing art and heritage precinct with must visit museums, art galleries, churches and synagogues. The airports are an hour away. For those who would like to experience fine dining in style, we host 9 of the city’s most acclaimed restaurants and bars, renowned for delectable cuisines from India, Europe, the Middle East and the Orient. Relish authentic Indian cuisine at Masala Kraft; world famous Japanese dishes at Wasabi by Morimoto; exquisite Eastern Mediterranean food at Souk and Chinese at Golden Dragon. Dine all day at Shamiana and choose from the exotic range of sumptuous desserts at La Patisserie. Unwind with a refreshing meal at Aquarius, the poolside restaurant in Mumbai; and visit the stylish Harbour Bar. Signature experiences such as the afternoon tea at Sea Lounge and private dining at the Chef’s Studio make your stay with us truly memorable. Mumbai’s original luxury hotel has 11 newly refurbished halls and venues, ideal for occasions ranging from formal meetings to elaborate weddings. The Ballroom, spacious enough for 450 guests, is perfect for conferences and grand private events. You could opt for a private dinner or yacht party if you are looking to entertain in true style. Our globally acclaimed Golden Keys Concierge would be happy to help, and caters to all your requirements in the city. Come, experience the legend.</string>
</resources>